[Heather] How about tomorrow,
early afternoon, does that work?
Yeah, so let's set that up for tomorrow,
and then we'll move forward
with everything. I'm excited.
That pizza looks good. Then again,
I'm ready to eat everything. Hi.
Okay, have a good day.
-Working hard or hardly working, bitch?
-[Heather] Working hard.
[Maya] Are you getting
your nail appointment?
Trying to support the family. Tarek said
I needed to put more work in.
[Heather laughs]
-You think you're gonna get the listing?
-[Heather] She promised me.
-Good.
-That's what I'm hoping.
Hi, ladies,
here's some menus for you guys.
-I might order that pizza.
-You gonna have pizza?
[Maya] No, I'm gonna do
the peanut butter smoothie.
-Or the milkshake? Is it milkshake-y?
-I can make it a milkshake.
-Sure.
-That sounds really good.
-Sweet potato fries.
-I'll have water for lunch, thank you.
Okay. Sounds good.
-[Christine] You know Mary got a new car?
-[Maya] Did she?
So she closed Doheny and got a new car.
[Maya] Jason does
feed Mary leads all the time.
She doesn't have to worry about that--
…all the time, that is for sure.
It's like this, it's like this,
it's like this, it's like this.
And we're over here like, what the--?
-All for Mary.
-Give us some plates.
-Mary gets all the pie.
-Give us something! It's true.
[Heather] Have you ever
gotten anything from Jason?
Yeah. It was in the beginning,
and it was once.
Yeah. Brett did put me on Sunset Plaza,
and so that was sweet of him--
-[Christine] Yeah.
-[Maya] But that's Brett. I gave Jason
a lot of deals. It's his company,
he can do whatever he wants to do.
-It just kind of suck for us.
-[Christine] Thank you.
-Tough luck we didn't date Jason.
-[Heather] I know.
-[waiter] Sweet potato fries.
-[Maya] Thank you, that looks good.
-Everything looks good to me right now.
-[Christine] Thank you so much.
-[waiter] Not a problem.
-[Christine] The favoritism
is never gonna change. Jason tells me,
"The reason I'm so hard on you
is because I know
how capable you actually are.
-Yeah.
-"I understand also
that you're extremely alpha, so you
and I have a hard time communicating
because we butt heads."
And I think in this business,
it's all about ego with all these men,
-and that's what's frustrating.
-It's true.
I mean, most of the male agents,
they have egos.
-[Heather] Yeah.
-They do.
I don't like being around people
like that, like, those egotistic males.
-Yeah.
-I don't like it. It turns me off.
I wanna talk to Jason and say,
"Look, I wanna get
my broker's license in Florida,
and maybe be open
to open The Oppenheim Group there--"
Why don't you just be
your own fucking broker?
Would you ever…
Consider leaving?
["Lifeline" playing]
♪ I'll be the lifeline ♪
♪ I'll be the moon
I'll be everything you need ♪
♪ I'll be all that you do ♪
♪ Breakin' through the ceiling ♪
♪ Watch the sky rain down in pieces ♪
[Heather] Okay. Can we hold each other
down this hill?
-[Heather] God.
-[Amanza screams] Limited range of motion.
[Heather] Oh, it looks so much better.
-[Amanza] I actually kinda like the light.
-[Heather] Wow.
-I like the blonde wood.
-Me, too.
Oh, my gosh.
This place is looking so good.
I just hope that everything
continues to go well
because I'm still trying
to prove myself to everyone,
and I have to prove it to myself, too.
[Amanza] Hello?
-Hi.
-Hello.
-How are you?
-[Heather] Good to see you.
Are you stressed?
Maybe a little.
Are we gonna be stressed?
-Uh… I think so.
-Yes, you more than us.
Really?
I don't know if you guys are aware,
but the floor situation
got a little out of control.
[Amanza] What do you mean?
-What's going on?
-It was water damage that comes in
-from the patio, by the pool.
-[Amanza] How much extra?
So it's going to be 5,000 dollars more.
-Just for the floors?
-For the floor repair.
When are the floors gonna be finished?
Because you can't do anything else
until then.
We need to be done within two weeks.
-Yeah, that's not gonna--
-[Angel] We'll try to get it done,
-the guys will work late.
-Trying to rush everybody
to be able to have it on time,
we have to pay expediting fees for that.
This is not gonna go over well at all.
Jason's scary. [laughs]
You know, he's intimidating.
He's a tough boss
and he expects a lot from us.
When a lot of money is involved,
and it's his money
that he's fronting for this house,
I don't wanna give him the bad news,
and I don't wanna hear what he has to say.
So the floor, 5,000 extra dollars,
and an extra week.
Yeah.
Okay. So, we were hoping
to keep the total around 25,000.
So are we at 30,000 now?
Actually, it's 38,000 right now.
-Thirty-eight?
-What's the extra 8,000?
The-- the extra manpower to try to get
everything done as quick as we can.
I don't see anybody working.
We're basically paying more and we're
not done in time. Jason's gonna flip out.
I know he will understand if you guys--
-Oh, you do? Have you ever met Jason?
-[Amanza, Joe laugh]
-So you call him.
-No. Good luck, you guys.
-He's like, "Good luck, bye."
-[Amanza, Joe laugh]
-Awesome.
-Wonderful. So you're gonna--
-Heather, you're gonna call him?
-No, you're gonna call him.
Just tell Mary to call him.
Yeah…
Rochambeau call Jason? [chuckles]
Rock, paper, scissors? [scoffs]
Okay.
[Amanza screams]
I'm gonna start out by saying, "Jason,
I want you to know, I was early today."
-[Amanza laughs]
-You were 15 minutes late, girl.
I won't tell him though
because he's already gonna be pissed.
-Like, this is bad.
-[Amanza] Better to be pissed off
-than to be pissed on.
-[Jason] Hey.
Hey, Jason.
Heather wants to tell you something.
[Jason] Okay.
Hi, are you in a good mood right now?
Yeah, are you happy?
Are you in a good mood?
[Jason] Why're you asking me if I'm
in a good mood? What's the bad news?
Well, Amanza has something to tell you.
-[Jason] Oh, great.
-[Amanza] Okay. The quote for the floors,
they found unforeseen water damage,
and they have to do,
like, 5,000 extra dollars worth of work
on the floors.
Alright, well, it's manageable.
And then also, there was no way
he could get it done,
even remotely close to our deadline.
Yeah. So because of the time frame,
they're having to hire more men
and work longer hours, so our…
Oh, God. Our budget, yeah, is at
-thirty-eight thousand.
-And they need an extra week.
[Jason] Shit! So now we gotta just
push everything back. Ugh.
We gotta run it by the clients, obviously.
I don't think they'll be happy
with the delay, but, you know,
I don't think they have much choice.
We gotta get this done.
At the end of the day, it's really on us.
We're the ones
that have to sell it in time.
So we're just making our job harder.
Do everything that needs to be done.
I'll front the 38,000.
Okay.
[Jason] Keep me posted on things
'cause I gotta apprise the clients
of all this stuff and make sure
that we get approval.
-Okay.
-[Jason] Not gonna stress out,
I'm gonna let you guys stress out.
If you're not stressed out, we're not.
The most stressful thing
was this call to you.
-We almost had Mary do it.
-[both laugh]
[Jason] Don't think
that that's gonna help.
-Okay. Rolling my eyes over here.
-Okay, good. Alright. [laughs]
-[Jason] Alright, bye.
-[Amanza, Heather] Bye.
He's in a good mood, right?
-[Amanza] Seriously.
-What's going on?
-Brett and Jason have been really, like--
-Are they medicating? [laughs]
Oh, I bet you.
["Do Your Thing" playing]
♪ Wake up and I'm ready to roll ♪
'Cause I know where I'm goin' ♪
♪ It don't matter how long it takes
'Cause I'm in control ♪
♪ Oh oh oh yeah yeah yeah
You can keep your eyes on me ♪
Imma do my thang ♪
♪ Imma do it, do it ♪
[Chrishell] This is Valley Village.
It's a really cute area.
Super, super residential.
-[Mary] It seems very quiet, which I like.
-[Chrishell] Yeah.
It is in the middle
of being completely redone.
-[Chrishell] Be careful when you get out.
-[Mary] Alright.
-[Mary] Oh, yeah.
-[Chrishell] Yeah.
[Mary] Romain and I wanna do a flip.
We've been, you know,
casually looking at homes for a while.
So now that we're married,
and I just sold my previous listing,
I think it's time to really get serious
and start looking.
Because I can save commission on my end,
and Romain can do
a lot of the work himself,
which saves us a lot of money.
It's definitely a work in progress.
-[Mary laughs] Full-on construction site.
-[Chrishell] Yes. Did you wear heels?
-Yeah, I've got boots on, so I'm good.
-Alright.
Mary and Romain are looking for a house,
possibly to flip.
A huge perk of being a realtor
is that a lot of times
we know about listings
that either aren't on the market
or it's going to be a while
until they hit the market.
So you can really get in
before there's any competition.
[Chrishell] Eventually,
you're going to be looking at
four bedroom, three and a half bathroom.
Over 2,500 square feet.
Actually, this is--
So this is one of the smaller bedrooms,
perfect for an office.
And then…
in here you come into
the big open kitchen.
-You can imagine--
-[Mary] Kind of open living.
-Use your imagination.
-[Mary] I like that.
And this is actually
on a 9,000-square-foot lot.
So you have quite a bit of space outside,
as well.
[Mary] Oh, wow.
[Chrishell] Oh!
There's going to be a pool.
That's super cool. You can do barbecue.
So the price on this right now,
he's looking to enter the market
around 1.7.
-I know that's high.
-Yeah.
But that's him thinking once it's
completely finished entering the market.
There's a big pro to selling it before you
even have to mess with the market.
-Right.
-[Chrishell] So I know he's flexible
and he would probably come down from that.
And like I said, this is kind of,
if you don't wanna do a full-blown flip.
Could be best of both worlds,
potentially…
-[Chrishell] Right. And I think--
-…if we can get it at a lower price
-before it hits the market.
-[Chrishell] Right.
[Chrishell] And then,
what everyone wants to see,
his and her closets.
-Don't look.
-[Mary] Wait, which one's bigger?
The secret to a long marriage?
His and hers bathrooms and closets.
-They're the same.
-It's the same.
[Chrishell] And then you've got
the master bedroom.
-Access right through to the pool.
-[Mary] Oh, I love that.
And the bathroom is amazing.
-[Mary] Oh, yeah.
-[Chrishell] Really nice. There's still
some finishes that you could choose.
Oh, one second. I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
-I'll take this real quick,
-but I'll meet you in there in one second.
-Totally fine.
But it could work. Like, the size is good.
Have you talked to the caterers
for the charity event?
Like, four bedrooms, perfect.
So when your parents,
Austin, friends wanna stay over.
If we ever decide
if we wanted to stay here for a while
and then, that's if we want to…
start a family or anything,
then we'll have the room for it.
Did you get the result?
I did get the results, yeah.
What did you get?
[giggles] What do you think I got?
I don't know. You always said
that you were, like, really fertile, so…
-I mean…
-[laughs] Well… I still am.
I am Fertile Myrtle.
But they do still recommend
us freezing either eggs or embryos,
-like, right away because every--
-Just in case.
Every year, like,
the number of good eggs, like, diminishes.
-We don't have to.
-[chuckles]
-But… if we want to--
-But we have to.
-We can freeze them.
-We have the option.
Congratulations.
You married a very fertile old lady.
-[Romain sighs]
-[Mary laughs]
I have no doubt on that. [laughs]
It wouldn't be awkward at all to have
my 23-year-old son come stay with us
-while we have a newborn. [laughs]
-Yeah.
-[Mary] Not weird at all.
-[Romain] Not at all.
["Make You Want It" playing]
♪ I make you want it so bad
I make you want it… ♪
[Christine] This hair today is just, like…
-so fucking curly, man. It sucks!
-It is super curly.
So I guess we're having,
a Friendsgiving at the office.
Mm, are you gonna go?
Yeah, I guess I have to. [laughs]
It could be nice.
The food's gonna be really good.
Ah! This is Chanel!
[Christine] Ugh, sorry.
These dogs have no sense of style.
Um, I wanna talk to you for a second.
Jason was hard on you the other day.
[Davina] He's always, you know,
busting my butt, man.
I feel like, even when I was arguing
with Jason at Brett's house,
it made me feel good to notice
that everybody came to back me up.
-Obviously, you…
-Yeah.
-Mary didn't, but everyone else--
-[Davina] Mary certainly didn't.
She was the one person that didn't, right?
I have to defend Jason on this.
Of course you have to defend him.
I'm not really sure why Jason keeps
giving Mary co-listing properties.
Maybe it has to do with their personal
relationship when they were dating.
I mean, I've never worked anywhere that…
you know, one of the so-called equals
had priority treatment because of their--
I mean, it's unusual.
How does he not see that all of us,
except for him and Mary,
are telling him, like,
"Hey, you know, you're being
really tough on us. And me.
You're really heavily favoring Mary,
and it's a little unfair."
Mary has Stockholm Syndrome.
That's a whole other thing.
Everything that Jason said,
she's like,
"Yes, yes, master. That's right. Yes."
I feel like the only people that speak up
about it are, like, me, you and Maya.
Like, that's it.
Has Maya voiced her opinion,
though, to Jason or to Mary?
I actually had lunch
with Maya and Heather.
And Maya kind of brought it up,
and we were talking about the favoritism.
She's really fed up, and she's like,
"I don't know how much longer
I can take this, Mary getting listing
after listing, and I'm busting my ass.
I might just go back to Miami
if this continues."
If she feels that way, I totally get it.
I mean, no one wants to feel
like their work isn't recognized.
I mean, that totally sucks.
If Maya leaves…
That will be the straw
that broke the camel's back.
Jason is oblivious to the line in the sand
at the office,
when he's created that divide.
If he doesn't watch out, people are gonna
get fed up with it and bounce.
It's a lot. It's a lot to put up with.
It's already hard enough as it is,
you know…
-I know.
-…in real estate. So I feel like,
if you're not supported,
then it's pretty much impossible.
♪ Can't harsh my vibe
Can't kill my mellow ♪
♪ Had me at hello, hello, hello ♪
♪ Had me at hello ♪
Hi.
How are you?
-How are you?
-[Kat] Good.
Thank you so much
for letting us use the art for the house.
-Yeah.
-It's exciting.
-Is Amanza coming?
-She's actually not, she had a personal
-issue. So I'm filling in for her.
-Okay.
Amanza called me this morning,
super stressed out,
asking if I could cover
at the art gallery today,
picking out art for our concierge house.
And poor thing has to go to court
and fight to get full custody
of her children.
So… yeah, of course,
I'm gonna cover for her and help her out.
But…
unlike her, I will not reveal
any personal information
regarding her situation.
I'm not the expert like she is,
-but I'm gonna do my best.
-Okay.
[upbeat rock playing]
Well, this will be the first time
either of us have been to the courthouse
and we weren't getting a divorce.
-That's sad. Oh, my God.
-[both laugh]
How are you feeling
about taking on full custody?
I mean,
the only thing that makes me nervous is
just how much responsibility…
-Doing it on your own?
-Like double time.
I get it, you know,
he's gotta be away.
-[Mary] Yeah.
-[Amanza] I'm excited to have them more.
I'm just slightly stressed out
about being able to feed them,
keep clean clothes on their back.
[Mary] It could be worse.
I'm headed to the courthouse today,
to initiate the process
of getting full custody for my kids.
My ex is not in the picture right now.
So this is the best thing for them.
[Amanza] This place is so depressing.
Everybody's going through
a bad custody thing or something.
It's one of the reasons
why I wanted you to come with me.
[Mary] Well, I got you.
[Amanza laughs]
I'd honestly rather be anywhere else
but the Los Angeles courthouse right now.
Like, maybe picking art with Heather
for our project.
But I gotta do what I gotta do.
And this is what's best for my kiddos.
[Heather] It's my first time picking art
for a home.
I'm excited.
I actually don't like going to museums
and art gallery things,
but Kat's studio is probably
my absolute favorite art gallery…
Well, I've actually never gone
to an art gallery. [laughs]
[Kat] Do you know
what the staging looks like?
That's the problem. I don't know.
Amanza's taking care of that.
-[Kat] Alright, let's take a look.
-[Heather] Okay.
This piece is actually
by my favorite artist.
-This is Flore.
-Flore, okay.
I love this. I love all the colors.
-Yeah.
-[Heather] I'm trying to think, maybe…
living room or master bedroom?
-Yeah, I think so.
-[Heather] What else?
-[Kat] This is Punk Me Tender.
-Poke Me Tender?
-[Kat] Punk Me Tender. Yeah.
-Punk Me Tender.
[Heather] I like the colors.
-Maybe for the office, actually.
-[Kat] That could work.
-[Heather] Wow, this is cool.
-This piece, Jason actually just
-purchased.
-[Heather] Okay.
What is this?
This piece is by Charles Patrick.
It's international currency,
cut into tiny, little butterflies.
Oh, I love it.
This is amazing.
I love this.
I like this. I love the lion.
Oh, I love this. Okay.
I think I'm loving this.
I love that.
This one could be good
for the wall by the piano.
What about this one
for above the fireplace?
Loving this for the master bedroom.
I don't know. There's so much great stuff.
[Heather] I don't know what to do.
I don't know. I'm just crossing my fingers
and hoping for the best.
Let's see if these are load-bearing walls,
if we can open up across there…
-That's gonna be awesome. Yeah.
-[Christine] It'll be really cool.
Once you clean the hill up,
this view's amazing.
-[doorbell rings]
-That's Lisa. Hold on.
[Christian] Okay.
Lisa planned our engagement party.
-I want Cirque du Soleil performers.
-[Lisa] Okay.
-[Christine] Can we fly them from Vegas?
-For sure.
What is happening?
And now she's planning our wedding.
If anyone can pull off a spectacle,
it's Lisa.
She can practically read my mind.
-[Christine] Hey, girl.
-[Lisa] Hi, babe, how are you?
[Christine] You look so good, how are you?
This is the furthest I've ever gotten
with wedding planning, so…
I give myself a pat on the back.
I've been engaged a few times,
but this is the first time
it's all coming together.
It's kind of nerve-wracking,
but in a good way.
I just hope
I don't turn into Julia Roberts.
Like in Runaway Bride, on a horse. Again.
-Alright.
-[Lisa] Oh, my gosh, guys.
-What are you working on?
-Home renovations, round two.
You're doing renovation and the wedding?
-[both] Yeah.
-Oh, my God, you guys are crazy.
-[Christian laughs]
-[Christine] We're aware. Yeah.
-So let's talk wedding.
-[both] Let's do it.
What are you guys thinking about vision,
any kind of theme?
-So I wanted to get married in a church.
-[Lisa] Okay.
[Christine] Like, a beautiful cathedral
of sorts.
-Okay.
-[Christine] I'm thinking for the theme,
like, a Gothic winter wonderland.
I want it to, like, snow somehow.
It's cool. You don't get that in L.A.
You guys have any desires for food?
Pastas, truffles…
-She loves truffles.
-All the finest things.
-Yeah, all over the place. Yeah, and--
-[Christine] Pizzas, fried things.
Yeah… that's more you. [laughs]
-[Lisa] What about the wedding cake?
-I thought it'd be beautiful
if we could figure out
how to do a white cake with strawberries
and make them bleed down somehow,
like when you open it.
-'Til death do us part vibes.
-[Christian] Got it.
[Christine] I want the cake to be
black on the outside, but you open it,
-and surprise, it's white.
-[Lisa] Okay.
Black on the outside, white on the inside,
with the red. Got it. Yeah.
Sorry. Just keeping up here,
just keeping up.
-Perfect.
-It's got to be grand.
[Lisa] Okay.
Any live bands for music, guys?
I mean we could do--
But I don't want like…
-[mimics brass band]
-[Lisa] No.
-I don't want any of that shit.
-Okay.
-[Lisa] So a live band, just not cheesy.
-Yeah. A good live band.
-Perfect. Are we doing a bridal party?
-I don't wanna do the bridesmaid thing.
I decided not to have a bridal party
'cause it's so distracting.
The last thing I wanna see is
people crying,
wheezing and sneezing
in their fucking beige dresses and shit,
swaying because they're too drunk.
I don't wanna do it.
So do we have an approximate guest count?
Have you guys talked about
guest lists at all?
-No bitches. No buffet. No speeches.
-[Lisa laughs]
-It's gonna be a tight list.
-Yeah, that's it.
We were trying to get this done
in two months.
[Lisa laughs]
Is that realistic?
I know two months is quick, but that's why
you hire people to do these things.
♪ How do you like me now?
Whoa whoa ♪
♪ I'm gonna show you what I'm made of ♪
♪ How do you like me now?
Whoa whoa ♪
♪ I'm gonna show you I was born for this ♪
♪ How do you like me now?
Whoa whoa… ♪
-Man, this looks good.
-Oh, man.
[Jason] This place looks awesome.
-[Brett] How many people was it, 40?
-[Jason] Damn. It's like torture,
walking around here.
We've been doing Friendsgiving
at the Oppenheim Group
for, I think, five years now.
This night is the confluence
of all of my favorite things.
It's all my family
and all my closest friends.
The food is epic.
It's, like, my favorite meal of the year
and my favorite night of the year,
all in one.
We're lucky, man.
Great friends, great family.
Yeah.
-It's gonna be fun.
-It's a cool day.
I like it right now when it's just us,
no one's here.
[laughs] All this food.
-[Romain] The food is ready?
-[Mary laughs] Hey!
-How pretty.
-[Jason] I did it myself. Come on in.
Hey, babe. Thanks for making it.
-Wow. It's so big.
-So pretty.
-[Jason] Happy Thanksgiving, beautiful.
-Happy Thanksgiving.
[Mary] Are you eating already?
-[Romain] No.
-You look nice, Ma.
-Thank you.
-[Jason] Mama. Oh, good to see you.
JT in the house.
-Hi, guys.
-Damn, girl. How are you?
[Romain] Aïe, aïe, aïe,
you gonna be in trouble.
-[Chrishell] Should we sit?
-[Maya] Are we sitting down?
[screams] Oh, my God!
Boob almost fell out. [giggles]
[Jason] Chrishell,
your dream has come true with that bell.
You are the inspiration.
We need a bell. Every time someone
closes something, we, like, ring the bell.
[Chrishell] I am so excited.
-I can't wait to, like…
-[Jason] You're the official bell ringer.
One hit per million.
Jason, that's giant.
-If I had a nickel…
-Oh, my God.
-All right, everyone…
-[glasses clinking]
…dinner time!
[Mary laughs] Don't have to tell me twice.
-Let's do it.
-[Brett] Go ahead.
-I should've brought a vegan pumpkin pie.
-[Brett] I'm gonna taste it.
-[Chrishell] You feeling brave?
-[Jason] Do a little bit more dark meat.
-[Mary] What's this thing?
-[Chrishell] It's macaroni that's sweet.
[Heather] I don't know if I can have this.
[Chrishell] I thought there was just
one station. I didn't know
-it was gonna keep going like this.
-[Heather] I'll get veggies.
-[Maya] Mashed potatoes, nice.
-[Jason] Best thing here.
-[Mary] What is it?
-[Heather] Is there butter? I don't know
-if there is.
-[Jason] Very high class, so it's good.
I can't believe I'm drinking
Oppenheim Group wine. Jesus Christ.
Seconds, Pops?
[Christine] That's how you know
I was desperate.
-It's not good. I don't like it at all.
-It's not, it's awful.
I'm actually excited to leave
on a holiday. I usually always just do
something with family,
so it's fun to get away.
-[Chrishell] Where are you guys going?
-We're doing Amsterdam first, then Paris.
-[Chrishell] For Thanksgiving?
-Mm-hmm.
Are you expecting anything special
to happen in Paris?
It's always risky to take a girl to Paris,
because they're always
gonna be expecting something.
I don't know. I feel, like, I don't wanna
go into it with expectations.
Of course, I'd say yes,
and I can't wait to marry him, but…
um, I can wait as well.
I have a feeling.
Well, we are having dinner
with his jeweler later tonight, so…
-[Chrishell] Are you serious? Oh, my Gosh!
-[Jason] No way.
-And we did try on rings, so…
-[Jason] Oh, wow.
[Mary] Yeah, it's happening. [laughs]
-Can you send us a group text
if it happens?
-[Maya] We don't wanna find out
-on Instagram.
-No.
Hey, guys. Where's Amanza?
You're doing the project with her.
Does she even show up at all?
-Like, she helps?
-[Heather] It's a lot of stress on me
'cause Amanza is staging,
but she couldn't show up.
-So I had to go pick art for the house.
-You went to the gallery?
-[Heather] She's doing personal stuff.
-Aren't we all, though?
[laughter]
I mean, I have a good eye, I think.
I just hope it looks good with the--
I don't know
how the furniture's gonna look.
[Maya] I call her Messy Nancy.
-I know.
-It's always something.
-[Christine, Maya] She's late, sick…
-[Maya] Then she doesn't show up,
-she forgot her phone in an Uber.
-I know.
She break into an open house.
There is always, like, an event.
This whole situation
with Amanza and her kids
is just really taking a toll on her.
It's heartbreaking to watch Amanza
and those two beautiful kids
go through all of this.
I think it's very important
that she spends this quality time
on Thanksgiving with her kids.
And that's something
that she needs to tell everybody.
It's not my place.
[Heather] So excited for the wedding.
Oh, my God,
our cake is gonna be really pretty.
I can't wait till you see it.
[Jason clinks a glass] Guys.
Quick toast.
Listen, everybody,
this is my favorite evening of the year.
All my friends and family,
all my cousins, aunts, uncles,
my best friends and co-workers.
So much to be thankful for
on this Thanksgiving,
so I couldn't be happier.
I love all of you, and I just wanna toast
to how fortunate we all are.
-[Heather] Cheers to that.
-[all] Cheers, everyone.
Sorry, and there's one more thing
that I'm thankful for.
I just closed
on a 44 million dollar house.
[all] What?
[screaming, applause]
Cheers!
[Mary] Oh, my God!
[Jason] The biggest sale
in the history of the Oppenheim Group.
[Mary repeating] I had a feeling.
Oh, my God!
I wish it was me. I mean, it would be nice
to sell a 43 million dollar listing.
Would be a nice commission.
But you know what?
Jason worked hard, and he deserve it,
so I'm not going to hate,
I'm going to congratulate.
So congratulations, Jason.
Mazel tov!
-Chrishell, would you go ring the bell?
-Oh, can I?
Yeah.
[cheering, applause]
-[bell clanging loudly]
-[wild cheering]
[Heather] Yes, your dream come true!
-[Chrishell] That's so exciting!
-I know, thank you, guys.
You kept this a secret from us?
-Who is the buyer, Jason?
-I can't say.
I signed an NDA,
so I can't really say much.
Remember when we were talking?
I was giving you shit?
Remember, I had a showing
the next morning?
Yeah? Oh, that one!
-Jason, I'm so happy for you.
-[Jason] Thank you, guys. Me too.
-[Chrishell] Let's have dessert.
-[Brett] Come on, dessert. Let's go!
Boom. I waited all year for this.
[laughs]
-Jason.
-[Jason] Hey.
-I just wanna say congratulations.
-Oh, thank you, honey.
Sorry I gave you a hard time
the other day.
Oh, come on.
That's amazing
that you put that in escrow.
I am really excited for Jason
that he sold Hillside.
I know how hard it is 'cause I was, like,
trying to sell my expensive listing.
No, you don't have to ever apologize.
I feel like I'm too tough on you.
That's sweet. Thank you.
The reason I'm so tough on you is
'cause, honestly, you have more potential
-than anyone I can think of.
-I appreciate that.
I just value your time tremendously,
and I think that you should, too.
Absolutely, I agree with you. [laughs]
[Jason] Honestly, if I wasn't hard on you,
that's when you should be concerned.
I'm only hard on people
that I really believe in.
'Cause it takes energy
to be engaged and to care.
-A hundred percent. Yeah.
-So, if I'm never upset,
then you're doing something wrong.
Good.
Oh, my God, I do want dessert.
Let's get dessert.
-Oh, my God. That bourbon-pecan--
-That blueberry pie is--
-Mary.
-Yeah?
You did a great job on Doheny.
I'm gonna bring you on Alpine.
[Mary] Oh, my God.
-That is awesome!
-That's exciting.
I have a client in Beverly Hills
who is looking to sell his property
for about 9.5.
-[Jason] You ready for that?
-Thank you! Yes, I'm ready.
-[Jason] Gonna rely on you, so…
-I'm all yours.
-Easy.
-[Jason, Mary laugh]
Can't be stopped.
[Maya] Are you kidding me?
I get it. We cannot expect Jason
to give all of us deals.
I'm just saying, maybe share a little bit
because we all work hard, and…
I just feel like,
at times, it's a little bit unfair.
In this business, you always have
to hustle no matter what, right?
Because nobody giving you anything.
It's just hurting a little bit
to see that someone gets more than us.
'Cause, you know that with Jason and Mary,
like, of course she's closing,
of course she does things,
because he gives her buyers,
listings, so it's easy.
Jason and I have been friends
for probably 15 years.
We dated for maybe a year of that.
These girls are trying
to take away all of my success
and my hard work, saying,
"Oh, it's 'cause they dated."
No!
I bust my ass, and I've worked for it.
And I think it's extremely rude
and disrespectful
to try to take my accomplishments and my--
all of my hard work away from me
because I'm a successful woman,
and they wanna throw it back on,
"She's probably sleeping with him."
No!
But what about the rest?
We all work hard, we all do open houses.
Like, when are we gonna be good enough,
you know?
["Not Worth It" playing]
♪ Fool me once, fool me twice
On purpose ♪
♪ I don't play all your games
You lie-ie-ie ♪
♪ You're not worth it… ♪